The implementation of sliding windows is very slow,
滑动窗口实施起来非常慢
but it can be faster if you choose a stride so that
但是如果你选择的步长使每个窗口
each window covers a new part of an image and there's no overlap.
都能覆盖图像的一个新区域并且没有重叠的话 速度会更快
Inspired by this approach,
受到此方法的启发
YOLO uses a grid instead of sliding windows.
YOLO 使用网格而不是滑动窗口
So, let's see how this works?
我们来看看原理
In this example, we're using a seven by 10 grid.
在此示例中 我们使用 7x10 网格
In the yellow algorithm,
YOLO 算法使用的网格更精细
a much finer grid is used but the overall process will be the same.
但是整体流程一样
Now you might be wondering,
你可能会疑问
how can we get an accurate bounding box out of a grid?
如何从网格中获得正确的边界框？
This was one of the challenges with sliding windows too.
滑动窗口也存在这项挑战
How can you account for the fact that these grid cells are
如何解决这些网格单元
unlikely to match with the bounding box for an object?
不太可能与对象边界框匹配这一问题？
Well, the idea is that we can assign output vectors to each grid cell,
原理是我们可以向每个网格单元分配输出向量
so each cell will have an associated vector that tells us one,
使每个单元格都具有相关的向量
if an object is in that cell, two,
这个向量首先告诉我们该单元格中是否有对象
the class of that object,
其次 对象的类别是什么
and three, the predicted bounding box for that object.
第三点是该对象的预测边界框
In this way the bounding box coordinates do not have to be contained within a grid cell.
这样的话 边界框坐标不需要包含在网格单元中
Assuming we have an input image with two labels and bounding boxes,
假设有一个具有真实标签和边界框的输入图像
we can then train a CNN to produce
我们可以训练 CNN 为每个网格单元
the correct output vectors for each of these grid cells.
生成正确的输出向量
We'll call the output vector for each grid cell gn.
我们将每个网格单元的输出向量称为 gn
This output vector contains the same parameters
这个输出向量包含的参数
as the output vector y we saw in previous videos.
与在上个视频中看到的输出向量 y 的一样
For the first cell, the vector g1 will look like this,
对于第一个单元格 向量 g1 看起来这样
there are no objects in this grid cell,
这个网格单元中没有对象
so PC equals zero.
因此 pc 等于 0
The vector will have zero for the class scores,
类别得分为 0
and some values for box coordinates.
方框坐标具有一些值
The values don't matter much because we'll discard vectors with too low of a PC value.
这些值的意义不大 因为如果 pc 值太低 我们将丢弃向量
We'll get the same output vector for all the grid cells that have no objects in them.
对于不包含对象的所有网格单元 输出向量都一样
Now what about this cell on top of the person in our image?
那么这个人上方的单元格呢？
This output vector which is numbered by grid cell looks like this,
这个按网格单元编号的输出向量看起来这样
PC equals one because there is an object in the grid cell,
pc 等于 1 因为该网格单元中有对象
and c1 equals one because the object is a person.
c1 等于 1 因为该对象是人
The output vector will also hold
输出向量中还包含
the predicted bounding box coordinates
预测的边界框坐标
and we'll see how these are generated later in this lesson.
我们将在后续部分了解如何生成这些值
Now that we know what the gn vectors look like,
我们一直知道 gn 向量是什么样的
let's see how we can use them to train a CNN.
我们将了解如何使用它们训练 CNN